Thomas	B-PERSON
Jefferson	I-PERSON
writes	O
the	B-WORK_OF_ART
Declaration	I-WORK_OF_ART
of	I-WORK_OF_ART
Independence	I-WORK_OF_ART

My	O
friend	O
Tom	B-PERSON
works	O
at	O
Google	B-ORG

Apple	B-ORG
announced	O
record	O
revenue	O
of	O
$81.8	B-MONEY
billion	I-MONEY
in	O
Q3	B-DATE
2024	I-DATE

